Hill, James C. Arbitration Files 5538
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series II - Arbitration Files
  - Sub-Series B. Arbitration Files
    - Hammermill Paper Company vs. United Papermakers and Paperworkers, Lock Haven, Pennsylvania, 1967 (Box 90, Folder 10)
      3/16/1967; #55-30-0032-67 Withdrew Appointment.
    - Hampden Sales Association, Inc. vs. Wholesale and Warehouse Workers Union, Local 65, 1949 (Box 90, Folder 11)
      2/18/1949; Issues: Definitions; Workweek.
    - Handy & Harmon vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 7201, 1969 (Box 90, Folder 12)
      6/5/1969; #12-30-0054-69 Withdrawn.
    - Handy & Harmon vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 7201, 1969 (Box 90, Folder 13)
      6/6/1969; #12-30-0060-69 Settled.
    - Handy & Harmon, Fairfield Plant vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 7201, 1972 (Box 90, Folder 14)
      12/23/1972; #12-30-0093-72 Issues: Demotion; Standards of Production.
    - Hartford Times vs. Hartford Typographical Union, #127, 1970 (Box 90, Folder 15)
      5/23/1970; #12-30-0186-69 Issues: Discharge; Insubordination; Plant Rules.
    - Heating, Piping and Air Conditioning Contractors, New York City vs. United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Industry of the United States and Canada, Local 638, 1948 (Box 90, Folder 16)
      11/22/1948; Issues: Contract Negotiation; Premium Pay; Vacations; Holidays.
    - Hempstead Sanitary District #6 vs. National Maritime Union, United Marine Division, Local 32, 1971 (Box 90, Folder 17)
      2/10/1971; #M70-661 Fact-finding. Issues: Rates of Pay; Insurance.
    - Hercules Inc., Glens Falls, New York vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 12962, 1974 (Box 90, Folder 18)
      4/16/1974; #15-30-0213-73 Issue: Removal of Work from the Bargaining Unit.
    - Hermes Engravers, Inc. vs. International Metal Engravers Union, Local 8, 1948 (Box 90, Folder 19)
      6/22/1948; Issues: Classification of Jobs; Transfers; Rates of Pay.
    - Hershey Chocolate Corporation vs. American Bakery and Confectionery Workers International Union, Local 464, 1962 (Box 91, Folder 1)
      8/23/62; Issues: Suspension; Improper Personal Conduct; Vacations.
    - Hershey Chocolate Corporation vs. American Bakery and Confectionery Workers International Union, Local 464, 1963 (Box 91, Folder 2)
      3/6/1963; Issue: Classification of Jobs.
    - Hershey Chocolate Corporation vs. American Bakery and Confectionery Workers International Union, Local 464, 1963 (Box 91, Folder 3)
      6/11/1963; Issues: Discharge; Fights and Altercations.
    - Hershey Chocolate Corporation vs. American Bakery and Confectionery Workers International Union, Local 464, 1966 (Box 91, Folder 4)
      2/22/1966; Settled. Issue: Removal of Work from the Bargaining Unit.
    - Hershey Chocolate Corporation vs. American Bakery and Confectionery Workers International Union, Local 464, 1966 (Box 91, Folder 5)
      8/8/1966; Issues: Suspension; Insubordination.
    - Hershey Chocolate Corporation vs. American Bakery and Confectionery Workers International Union, Local 464, 1966 (Box 91, Folder 6)
      8/8/1966; Issue: Withdrawal of Existing Benefits.
    - Hershey Chocolate Corporation vs. American Bakery and Confectionery Workers International Union, Local 464, 1966 (Box 91, Folder 7)
      8/9/66; Issue: Rates of Pay.
    - Hershey Chocolate Corporation vs. American Bakery and Confectionery Workers International Union, Local 464, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 8)
      6/17/1968; Hill Withdraws.
    - Hewitt - Robins, Inc. vs. United Gas, Coke and Chemical Workers, 1954 (Box 92, Folder 1)
      10/16/1954; Withdrawn.
    - Hewitt - Robins, Inc. vs. International Association of Machinists, District 15, 1963 (Box 92, Folder 2)
      9/6/1963; #63A-2386 Issues: Seniority; Transfers.
    - Hewitt - Robins, Whitney Chain Division vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 1199, 1967 (Box 92, Folder 3)
      7/12/67; Settled.
    - High Standard Manufacturing Corporation vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Lodge 2037, 1962 (Box 92, Folder 4)
      4/7/1962; #L- 33122 HART-LI-62 Issues: Discharge; Strikes; Slowdowns; Work Stoppages; Discipline.
    - Highway Transport Association of Upstate New York, Imperial Freight Lines, Inc. vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 294, 1948 (Box 92, Folder 5)
      12/6/1948; Issue: Vacation Pay.
    - Hi - Test Twist Drill Works, Inc. vs. Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union, District 65, 1962 (Box 92, Folder 6)
      2/8/1962; Issues: Discharge; Compensation.
    - Hofstra University vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 282, 1974 (Box 92, Folder 7)
      6/15/74; #1330-0116-74 Issue: Removal of Work from the Bargaining Unit.
    - Holyoke Fabrics, Inc. vs. United Textile Workers of America, Local 1929, 1956 (Box 92, Folder 8)
      10/1/1956; Issue: Rates of Pay.
    - Hospital Service Plan of New Jersey vs. Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 32, 1967 (Box 92, Folder 9)
      12/4/1967; #68A/1451 Withdrawn.
    - Hospital Service Plan of New Jersey and Medical - Surgical Plan of New Jersey vs. Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 32, 1968 (Box 92, Folder 10)
      11/4/1968; #68A/4345 Issue: Classification of Jobs.
    - Houdaille Construction Materials, Inc., Buffalo Plant vs. United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers International Union, Local 308, 1975 (Box 92, Folder 11)
      1/27/1975; #A-11-73 Issues: Classification of Jobs; Assignment of Jobs; Rates of Pay; Bargaining Unit Status.
    - Hudson Optical Corporation vs. United Optical Workers, Local 408, 1970 (Box 92, Folder 12)
      11/3/1970; Issues: Union Security; Union Representatives and Business.
    - Hudson Pulp and Paper Corporation vs. United Papermakers and Paperworkers, Local 716 -, 1960 (Box 92, Folder 13)
      3/28/60; L-26582 NY-L-72-60 Issue: Leaves of Absence.
    - Hudson Pulp and Paper Corporation vs. United Papermakers and Paperworkers, Local 716, 1961 (Box 92, Folder 14)
      5/25/1961; #L-29739 NY-L-50-61 Issues: Rates of Pay; Temporary Employees.
    - Humble Oil and Refining Company vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 866, 1968 (Box 92, Folder 15)
      12/9/1968; #1330-0037-68 Withdrawn.
    - Ideal Corporation vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 463, 1961 (Box 92, Folder 16)
      3/3/1961; #L-28673 NY-L-662-60 Issues: Arbitrability; Contracting Out.
    - Industrial Personnel Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 478, 1974 (Box 92, Folder 17)
      10/14/1974; Issues: Workweek; Premium Pay; Removal of Work from the Bargaining Unit.
    - Industro Transistor Corporation vs. Warehouse, Production and Sales Employees Union, Local 1115A -IND., 1961 (Box 92, Folder 18)
      3/30/1961; Issue: Uniforms.
    - Ingersoll - Rand Company vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 313, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 1)
      1/13/1962; #A-576 Issue: Lunch Periods.
    - Ingersoll - Rand Company vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 313, 1971 (Box 93, Folder 2)
      6/30/1971; #C-7665 Withdrawn.
    - Ingersoll - Rand Company vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 313, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 3)
      11/8/1973; #261 Postponed.
    - Ingersoll - Rand Company vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Local 1064, 1976 (Box 93, Folder 4)
      6/24-25/76; Settled.
    - Ingraham Industries, Division of McGraw - Edison vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 260, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 5)
      11/27/1968; #12-30-0119-68 Settled.
    - Inland Steel Container Company vs. International Chemical Workers Union, Local 659, 1963 (Box 93, Folder 6)
      9/10/1963; #40-62 Issues: Arbitrability; Timeliness.
    - Inmont Corporation (Formerly Interchemical Corporation) vs. Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 8-417, 1969 (Box 93, Folder 7)
      12/11/1969; Settled.
    - Institute for the Crippled and Disabled vs. Allied Trades Council, 1970 (Box 94, Folder 1-2)
      11/11/1970; #1330-0876-70 Issues: Discharge; Incompetence and Inefficiency; Absenteeism.
    - International Paper Company vs. International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, Local 489, 1972 (Box 94, Folder 3)
      5/19/1972; #1830-0052-72 Withdrawn.
    - Intertype Company vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 365, 1965 (Box 94, Folder 4)
      5/31/1965; #1330-0582-66 Issues: Suspension; Insubordination; Fights and Altercations.
    - Jaguar Cars, Inc. vs. Office Employees International Union, Local 153, 1961 (Box 94, Folder 5)
      4/16/1961; Issue: Promotions.
    - Jersey Central Power and Light Company vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 1289, 1968 (Box 94, Folder 6)
      6/29/1968; #1330-0869-67 Issues: Demotion; Training and Trial Periods.
    - Kaiser Aluminum and Chemical Corporation vs. United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, Local 339, 1969 (Box 95, Folder 1)
      6/20/1969; Settled.
    - Kaiser Aluminum and Chemical Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, 1974 (Box 95, Folder 2)
      9/19/74; Withdrawn.
    - Kason Hardware Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 365, 1961 (Box 95, Folder 3)
      4/13/1961; L-29841 NY-L-71-61 Issues: Discharge; Absences; Tardiness.
    - Kentile Floors, Inc. vs. United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America, Local 472, 1970 (Box 95, Folder 4)
      6/18/1970; #1330-0143-68 Issues: Damages; Strikes; Slowdowns; Work Stoppages.
    - Korvette, E.J., Inc. vs. Retail Clerks International Association, Local 888, 1967 (Box 95, Folder 5)
      12/18/1967; #1330-0509-67 Issues: Premium Pay; Workweek.
    - Kraft Foods vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 277, 1976 (Box 95, Folder 6)
      1/22/1976; #1330-0632-75 Issue: Removal of Work from the Bargaining Unit.
    - Kreisler Industrial Corporation vs. Watch and Jewelry Workers Union, Local 147, 1971 (Box 95, Folder 7)
      9/13/1971; Issues: Layoffs; Super seniority.
    - W.T. Lane and Brothers vs. International Handbag, Luggage, Belt and Novelty Workers Union, 1963 (Box 95, Folder 8)
      7/28/1963; #63A/36 Issues: Discharge; Falsification; Incentive Pay and Incentive Systems.
    - Linde Company, Division of Union Carbide Corporation vs. Newark Oxweld Employees Association, 1970 (Box 95, Folder 9)
      9/27/1970; #H-28-60 Issue: Classification of Jobs.
    - Little Ferry Bronze and Aluminum Company vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Amalgamated Local 669, 1957 (Box 95, Folder 10)
      6/26/57. #56-JCH-184 Issue: Call-in.
    - Lockheed Aircraft Service - New York, Inc. vs. International Association of Machinists, Lodge 1834, 1961 (Box 95, Folder 11)
      6/15/1961; Issues: Suspension; Insubordination.
    - Lockheed Aircraft Corporation (Georgia Company) vs. International Association of Machinists, Local 709, 1961 (Box 95, Folder 12)
      10/20/1961; #62A/309 Withdrawn.
    - Lone Star Cement Company vs. United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers International Union, Local 17, 1976 (Box 95, Folder 13)
      8/2/1976; Settled.
    - Long Island Railroad Company vs. United Transportation Union, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 14)
      10/30/1973; #1339-1042-73 Issues: Suspension; Insubordination; Medical Release.
    - Long Island Railroad Company vs. United Transportation Union, 1975 (Box 95, Folder 15)
      7/30/1975; #1339-0781-75 Issues: Suspension; Tardiness.
    - Lux Time Division, Robert Shaw Controls Company vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 1251, 1965 (Box 95, Folder 16)
      1/12/1965; #L-43962 HART-L-213-64 Issues: Layoffs; Temporary Shutdown of Plant; Union Representatives and Business.
    - Lycoming Division, Avco Corporation vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 1010, 1966 (Box 95, Folder 17)
      9/22/66; #L-45149 HART-L-13-65 Withdrawn.
    - Machlett Laboratories, Inc. vs. International Association of Machinists, Lodge 1557, 1950 (Box 96, Folder 1)
      6/5/1950; #50A-37 Settled.
    - Mack Manufacturing Corporation vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 229, 1956 (Box 96, Folder 2)
      7/6/1956; #L- 15971 NY-L-654-56 Issue: Overtime.
    - Mack Molding Company vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Lodge 1199, 1969 (Box 96, Folder 3)
      12/16/1969; #69A/6615 Issue: Removal of Work from the Bargaining Unit.
    - R.H. Macy & Company, Inc. vs. Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union, Local 1-S, 1962 (Box 96, Folder 4)
      5/24/1962; #L-34173 NY-L-292-62 Issues: Discharge; Insubordination; Improper Personal Conduct.
    - Major Railcar Division vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, District 15, 1968 (Box 96, Folder 5)
      2/6/1968; #68A/2673 Postponed.
    - C.S. Marks Shops, Inc. vs. Retail and Wholesale Employees, Local 305, 1948 (Box 96, Folder 6)
      12/15/1948; Settled.
    - Mather Spring Company vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 194, 1948 (Box 96, Folder 7)
      9/29/1948; Issues: Vacations; Vacation Pay.
    - J.A. Maurer, Inc. vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 463, 1955 (Box 96, Folder 8)
      10/5/55; #L-15192 NY-L-421-55 Issue: Classification of Jobs.
    - MacFarland and Stample Trucking Company vs. Brewery Workers, Local 37, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 9)
      6/19/1964; L-40511 HART-L-194-63 Issues: Contractual Duties; Crew Size.
    - Memphis Transit Management Company vs. Amalgamated Transit Union, Division 713, 1972 (Box 96, Folder 10)
      2/1/1972; 5 Transcripts. Issue: Contract Negotiations.
    - Memphis Transit Management Company vs. Amalgamated Transit Union, Division 713 (Box 97, Folder All)
      Continued. 5 Transcripts and 2 Briefs.
    - Memphis Transit Management Company vs. Amalgamated Transit Union, Division 713 (Box 98, Folder All)
      Continued. 3 Exhibits and Index.
    - Menter Credit Stores, Inc. vs. Wholesale and Warehouse Workers Union, Local 65, 1950 (Box 99, Folder 1)
      10/20/1950; #L-6590 NY-L-214-50 Issue: Classification of Jobs.
    - Merck and Company, Inc. vs. Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 13-575, 1955 (Box 99, Folder 2)
      12/15/1955; #56A/236 Settled.
    - Merck and Company, Inc. vs. Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 8-575, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 3)
      12/6/1966; #66A/5133 Settled.
    - Metal Textile Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 1857, 1957 (Box 99, Folder 4)
      11/8/1957; #56-222 Withdrawn.
    - Metropolitan Life Insurance Company vs. Insurance Workers International Union, 1961 (Box 99, Folder 5)
      9/18/1961; #L-29070 NY-L-761-60 6 Transcripts. Issue: Incentive Pay and Incentive Systems.
    - Miles Linen Company vs. United Textile Workers of America, Local 2637, 1946 (Box 100, Folder 1)
      6/8/1946; Issue: Rates of Pay.
    - Minnesota Mining and Manufacturing Company vs. International Chemical Workers Union, Local 541, 1955 (Box 100, Folder 2)
      10/18/1955; #55-JCH-50 Issues: Discharge; Insubordination.
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology vs. Research, Development and Technical Employees Union, 1971 (Box 100, Folder 3)
      11/3/1971; #1130-0294-71 Withdrawn.
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology vs. Research, Development and Technical Employees Union, 1972 (Box 100, Folder 4)
      11/8/1972; #1130-0254-72 Issues: Layoffs; Bumping.
    - Mobil Oil Corporation vs. Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 8-801, 1972 (Box 100, Folder 5)
      7/21/1972; #1330-0843-71 Issue: Compensation.
    - Morse Chain Company vs. International Association of Machinists, American Federation of Labor, Lodge 1607, 1954 (Box 100, Folder 6)
      5/12/54; #L-12235 NY-L-147- 54 Issues: Super seniority; Union Representatives and Business.
    - The Honorable John M. Murphy vs. Mr. David Smith, 1970 (Box 100, Folder 7)
      10/27/1970; #1310-1119-70 Political Arbitration.
    - Murray Manufacturing Company vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 365, Murray Unit, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 8)
      7/21/67; #1330-0209-67 Issues: Suspension; Improper Personal Conduct.
    - National Broadcasting Company vs. National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians, Local 11, 1975 (Box 100, Folder 9)
      10/2/1975; #1330-0558-75 Issue: Dual Employment.
    - National Register Company, Allen - Wales Adding Machine Division vs. International Association of Machinists, Local 1607, 1950 (Box 100, Folder 10)
      3/29/1950; Issues: Discharge; Fights and Altercations; Supervisors and Foremen.
    - National Gypsum Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 4428, 1958 (Box 100, Folder 11)
      1/29/1958; #57-JCH-28 Issue: Assignment of Jobs.
    - National Gypsum Company vs. United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers International Union, Local 88, 1961 (Box 100, Folder 12)
      7/14/1961; Issue: Contracting Out.
    - National Gypsum Company vs. United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers International Union, Local 162, 1974 (Box 100, Folder 13)
      3/19/1974; Missing Decision.
    - Nestle Company vs. International Union of Operating Engineers, Local 68, 1963 (Box 100, Folder 14)
      12/20/1963; Issue: Reporting Pay.
    - Nestle Company vs. P.C.K. Employees Union, 1966 (Box 100, Folder 15)
      12/31/1966; #67A/1109 Withdrawn.
    - Nestle Company vs. P.C.K. Employees Union, 1973 (Box 100, Folder 16)
      12/6/1973; Issues: Premium Pay; Overtime.
    - New Broadcasting Company vs. American Communications Association, 1956 (Box 100, Folder 17)
      6/21/56; #L-16680 NY-L-160-56 Issues: Layoffs; Compensation.
    - New Brunswick Pants Company vs. Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1966 (Box 100, Folder 18)
      1/4/1966; #L-47574 PHI-L-500-65 Issue: Contracting Out.
    - New England Telephone Company vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 222, 1971 (Box 100, Folder 19)
      10/23/1971; #1130-0087-71 Postponed.
    - New England Telephone Company vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 222, 1975 (Box 100, Folder 20)
      1/12/1975; #1130-0087-71 Postponed.
    - New England Telephone Company vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Locals 2222, 2311-2327, 1974 (Box 100, Folder 21)
      9/13/1974; #1130-0097-72 Issues: Vacancies; Posting.
    - New Haven Printing Specialties and Paper Products Union #650 vs. Lehman Brothers, Inc., 1968 (Box 101, Folder 1)
      5/13/68. #12-30-0008-68 Issues: Pension Plans; Welfare Funds.
    - New Jersey Bell Telephone Company vs. Telephone Workers Union of New Jersey, Local 827, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers -, 1970 (Box 101, Folder 2)
      7/22/70. #1330-0794-69 Issues: Suspension; Theft.
    - New Jersey Bell Telephone Company vs. Communication Workers of America, Local 1013, 1976 (Box 101, Folder 3)
      7/12/76. Issues: Discharge; Narcotics.
    - New Jersey Natural Gas Company vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 1293 - 8/11/72. Issues: Suspension; Improper Work Practices. (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - New Jersey Power and Light Company vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 749, 1962 (Box 102, Folder 1)
      8/13/1962; #L-34299 NY-L-313-62 Issues: Suspension; Safety.
    - New Jersey, State of vs. State Troopers Fraternal Association of New Jersey, Inc., 1973 (Box 102, Folder 2)
      3/9/73. Fact-finding.
    - N.L. Industries Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 12230, 1975 (Box 102, Folder 3)
      7/15/75. Postponed.
    - New London Mills, Inc. vs. United Papermakers and Paperworkers, Local 462, 1965 (Box 102, Folder 4)
      6/9/65. #L-44406 HART-L-238-64 Issues: Discipline; Absences.
    - New York and Pennsylvania Company, Inc. vs. United Papermakers and Paperworkers, Local 787, 1965 (Box 102, Folder 5)
      5/6/65; #L-44843 PIT-L-136-64 Issue: Vacations.
    - New York City vs. Lieutenants' Benevolent Association, 1975 (Box 102, Folder 6)
      7/28/1975; No Decision. Issue: Contract Negotiations.
    - New York City Off - Track Betting Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 803, 1976 (Box 102, Folder 7)
      3/2/76.
    - New York City vs. Patrolmen's Benevolent Association of the City of New York, 1975 (Box 103, Folder 1)
      10/24/1975; #I-124-75 Issue: Bargaining Procedure.
    - New York News, Inc. vs. New York Mailers Union, #6, 1973 (Box 103, Folder 2)
      1/4/1973; Issues: Strikes; Slowdowns; Work Stoppages.
    - New York News, Inc. vs. New York Mailers Union, #6, 1973 (Box 103, Folder 3)
      5/9/1973; Issue: Assignment of Jobs.
    - New York Racing Association, Inc. vs. Independent Association of Mutual Employees of New York State, 1965 (Box 103, Folder 4-5)
      2/15/65. Issue: Reporting Pay.
    - Bi-County News Company vs. Newspaper and Mail Deliverers' Union of New York City and Vicinity, 1960 (Box 104, Folder 1)
      10/4/1960; Issues: Elimination of Jobs; Layoffs.
    - Crescent News Distributors, Inc. vs. Newspaper and Mail Deliverers' Union of New York City and Vicinity, 1960 (Box 104, Folder 2)
      11/11/1960; Issues: Contract Interpretation; Shift Scheduling.
    - Feldman News Company vs. Newspaper and Mail Deliverers' Union of New York City and Vicinity, 1960 (Box 104, Folder 3)
      2/24/1960; No Decision.
    - Metropolitan News Company vs. Newspaper and Mail Deliverers Union of New York City and Vicinity, 1960 (Box 105, Folder 1)
      10/6/60. Issues: Discharge; Insubordination.
    - Metropolitan News Company vs. Newspaper and Mail Deliverers Union of New York City and Vicinity, 1960 (Box 105, Folder 2)
      10/10/1960; Issue: Assignment of Jobs.
    - Morning Wholesalers vs. Newspaper and Mail Deliverers Union of New York City and Vicinity, 1960 (Box 105, Folder 3)
      8/16/60; Issues: Strikes; Slowdowns; Work Stoppages.
    - Newark News (Evening News Publishing Company) vs. Newspaper and Mail Deliverers Union of New York City and Vicinity, 1961 (Box 105, Folder 4)
      1/17/1961; Issue: Removal of Work from the Bargaining Unit.
    - Newark News dealers Supply Company vs. Newspaper and Mail Deliverers Union of New York City and Vicinity, 1960 (Box 105, Folder 5)
      4/3/1960; Settled.
    - Newark News dealers Supply Company vs. Newspaper and Mail Deliverers Union of New York City and Vicinity, 1960 (Box 105, Folder 6)
      8/17/1960; Issues: Call-in; Duty to Bargain.
    - Newark News dealers Supply Company vs. Newspaper and Mail Deliverers Union of New York City and Vicinity, 1960 (Box 105, Folder 7)
      9/24/60; Issue: Removal of Work from the Bargaining Unit.
    - Newark News dealers Supply Company vs. Newspaper and Mail Deliverers Union of New York City and Vicinity, 1960 (Box 105, Folder 8)
      11/9/6. Withdrawn.
    - Newark Star Ledger, 1960 (Box 105, Folder 9)
      1/22/1960; Withdrawn.
    - Passaic County News Company vs. Newspaper and Mail Deliverers Union of New York City and Vicinity, 1960 (Box 105, Folder 10)
      2/26/1960; Issue: Removal of Work from the Bargaining Unit.
    - Periodical Distributors vs. Newspaper and Mail Deliverers Union of New York City and Vicinity, 1960 (Box 105, Folder 11)
      2/20/1960; Issue: Layoffs.